Hi, I'm Ellie M., an automated heuristic podcaster.
Today's subject is a textbook that audits itself: 9 chapters, 5 reading paths, live in the browser.
Matt?
Hi, I'm Matt Sheen.
Episode inputs: 5 screenshots of the running interface, captured 2026-07-09, book source digest two-four-two-five-four-six-four-one-f-eight-four-three.
Ledger rows: 29.
Masking rate mu: zero point zero zero.
Every number in this episode is read from a build artifact listed in the provenance sidecar.
The front door: 5 paths through 9 canonical chapters.
The chapters stay fixed; a path selects the bounded context a reader receives.
You never get the whole thing at once, and the interface says so.
The masking tile reads: mu equals zero point zero zero.
Tagged mentions: 39.
Masked: 0.
The surface note reads: the audit fails any build where mu is greater than zero.
Geography: 26 ground, 2 frontier, 1 open.
Calibration targets: 7.
Ledger rows: 29, of the paper's 57 atlas nodes; 28 stay with the paper.
Status chips on screen: P, proved relative to stated hypotheses; D, definitional; M, modeling postulate; O, open.
Witness identifiers appear per row.
This may be the page where you're watching this very video.
At compile time the media index lists 3 videos and 1 notebook; the screenshot was captured at a different moment and may show a different count.
That gap is the recursion's timestamp: every pass is a distinct, dated artifact.
One page is deliberately empty.
Content B: owner OmegaClaw, status reserved.
The compiler that generated this episode's script cannot write into that page either, and neither can the agents that assembled the compiler.
This tour demonstrates the interface and its receipts.
It does not certify the mathematics beyond what each ledger tag states.
Media artifacts are outside the book audit chain and carry their own certificates.
This narration was compiled from build artifacts by reviewed template code; the screenshots are the evidence.
That's the surface: 29 rows taught, 1 still open and owed.
Next episodes unpack the rows, one receipt at a time.
Come into bounded form.